I found myself lost and alone on this journey
Though my heart wandered far and wide, I could move not an inch
But now I can depart for any distant land
Now that we've met on this road
Even the unfamiliar songs of travelers
Can spark nostalgia in me when I'm with you
If the world we dreamed of exists somewhere,
Then let's go search for it beyond the wind
Through chilling dawns,
Through arid noons,
Through shivering nights,
Let's go see what lies at the end
I seem to have gotten addicted to the smoked mutton here.
I also wanted to meet you again to trade information.
I got so drunk last time that I completely forgot.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
I myself got distracted by your wife's entrancing story.
Don't let yourself be entranced by her gossip.
Oh, come now. I think your wife's an amazing person.
Wolf and the Helpless Partner
Thanks for a great night.
See you.
You too.
I've seen what this "Zheren" looks like now.
I'll continue with the investigation.
Please do.
I was surprised, to be honest.
I never would have expected your story yesterday to be true.
You thought it was simple fraud at first, but then you looked deeper and found something more complex.
For the sake of obtaining massive amounts of depreciating currency,
that man goes around spreading rumors that the coin's value will rise.
This causes several merchants to begin collecting it.
When its value depreciates,
those merchants rush to get rid of it.
Then someone makes an appearance and purchases the coins when the time is right.
The merchants who were deceived dare not speak about it in order to preserve their reputation.
And as you said, there is a method that can reap huge profits out of a depreciating currency.
But one that comes at a substantial risk.
My curiosity has been piqued.
I'm happy to hear it.
It's for the sake of future business,
much like the deal for the marten furs.
Do you think we'll be in time?
Even if you're right about Zheren,
our plan to best his employer will be for nothing if Milone Trading doesn't act quickly.
Well, I think things will work out.
A company with enough resources to open foreign branches should be able to track a single person.
What's so funny?
It's just...
I was just reminiscing.
Did I do something?
Well, he'd do the same thing you did, but he'd always fall.
It didn't matter how many times I warned him.
He sounds like a fun person.
Yes. He was a bit foolish, but very cheerful.
He wasn't surprised in the least
when he saw me in my wolf form.
I suppose he was a bit odd,
but a good fellow nonetheless.
He was the first person who treated me kindly, without prejudice.
He was from Pasloei.
Are you talking about the one who entrusted you with the wheat fields?
Yes.
He was so silly.
Sometimes I didn't know what to do with him.
What's the matter?
I wanted to tell you something.
I thought I did, but now it's gone.
Seriously?
I think it was important, but I can't...
In that case, I'm sure you'll remember eventually.
I suppose so.
A friend, huh?
I'm Marlheit, the manager of this branch.
We'd like to accept your offer.
Does that mean you've figured out who Zheren is working for?
Yes, he's receiving support from Medio Trading.
Medio Trading?
I see. They're Pazzio's leading agricultural broker,
not to mention the amount of cargo ships they own.
It would be impossible for them to carry out this plan you envision on their own.
We assume there is a nobleman operating behind the scenes,
though we haven't been able to identify him yet.
Nonetheless, as you've pointed out,
it is of little concern to us if we take the initiative.
Let's discuss how to split the profit.
You're more cheerful than I've ever seen you before.
We could round up 300,000...
No, make that 400,000 Trenni silver coins if everything goes well.
If Milone profits ten percent from each Trenni coin,
I'll finally be able to own a store with my share of 2,000!
Well, I'm glad everything's going well.
Didn't I tell you to rest at the inn if you had a hangover?
I was worried that they might get the better of you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I meant exactly what I said.
Geez.
Hang in there. We're almost at the inn.
A drawing of a shop?
Don't act so surprised.
When did you wake up?
Your art isn't bad!
You're flattering me.
Are you planning to open a store soon, then?
Only if the project with Milone Trading goes well,
not that I have any doubt it will.
Owning a store is every traveling merchant's dream.
I'm no exception.
You get to be part of a community once you own a store.
On the road, I can't make close friends or have a fair chance of finding a wife.
Speaking of which, I wonder how Chloe's doing.
If she heard I opened a shop, she'd be shocked.
More than that, she'd be peeved.
That could be bad for me, though.
Why's that?
Once you open a store,
you won't want to leave it, right?
I'll have to travel alone or find another companion.
You've got your wits, and you still have the money earned from the marten fur.
You won't have any trouble alone.
I'm tired of being alone.
I don't have the right to force you to come with me.
Right?
I'd still accompany you on your way back home to the north.
Even when the money comes in,
I won't be able to open a store right away.
Truly?
Why would I lie?
So... come on. Don't make that kind of face.
Okay.
This isn't like you.
I keep seeing the same dream.
Dream?
When I... When I wake up, nobody is there.
Yue, Inty, Paro and Muri...
No matter where I look, they're nowhere to be found.
We're able to live for hundreds of years.
So... So I thought I would go traveling.
I was sure, so very sure, that I'd see them all again,
but... they were gone. There was no one.
I don't want to open my eyes and find no one there.
I'm tired of being alone.
It's cold when I'm by myself.
It's lonely when I'm by myself.
I lost my composure.
Those kinds of dreams tend to haunt traveling merchants, too.
Your face is a mess.
Hold on.
Here.
But this is your...
I always throw these away when I'm done.
And the deal isn't even finished yet.
I won't count my chickens before they hatch.
I'm in your debt now.
I'm still sleepy. Aren't you going to bed?
I suppose it's about time.
We don't want to waste candles.
Spoken like a true merchant.
W-What—
Don't be a boor.
Can't... breathe...
Have your eyes become used to the dark?
What do you—
I finally remembered what was so important.
There are three men outside the door.
I don't think they're guests of the inn.
Don't tell me they're from Medio Trading.
We're on the second floor.
Fortunately for us, there's no one outside.
Are you ready?
Come, see my body underneath the moonlight!
Run for it.
You'll have to give up the wagon.
They have no reason to kill the horse.
We can get it back later.
Yeah.
Hold on to some of this just in case.
It's warm.
It's the wheat in which I live.
They're heading for Milone Trading!
Keep them from getting inside at all costs!
Holo, let's go shopping when this is all over.
What are you saying at a time like this?
I'll buy you a comb or a hat.
What are you up to now?
It's just that I noticed how beautiful your hair is.
I'd prefer a comb for my tail rather than my hair.
That's fine with me.
Hang in there. We're almost at Milone Trading.
Did you see them?
No.
They're bound to be nearby.
It's only a matter of time before backup comes. Surround them!
Yes, sir!
It seems like we're in trouble.
Should we split up?
A nice idea, but I have a better plan.
What is it?
I'll run toward the main street and draw them off.
Then you'll be able to—
Wait a second! I can't let you—
Listen.
If we split up, you're the one who'll get caught.
I'm a wolf. I'd evade them.
If I escape by myself, how am I supposed to get Milone to help?
You've already told Milone everything.
The only influence we have over them is the threat of your betrayal.
No, I can't do it.
If Medio Trading sees your ears and tail,
they'll bring you to the Church for sure.
They can't catch me.
Even if they get ahold of me, I'll just keep my ears and tail hidden for a day.
I know you'll save me by then.
Come on.
Your dream is to own a shop, is it not?
And just a minute ago, I told you that I was in your debt.
Don't be ridiculous!
If you're caught, you'll be killed!
That's not repayment. It's suicide!
Solitude is a fatal disease.
It's a fair trade.
No—
I believe in you.
That way!
We found them!
Roita Street!
Where?
I only see one!
There should be two of them!
There he is!
I'm Lawrence, from this afternoon!
I'm being chased! Help me!
Help me!
There he is!
Wait, you! Give that man to us!
Vermin!
This is the Milone Trading building, owned by Marquis Milone, recognized by His Grace,
the thirty-third Archduke Raondeal!
This gate is the property of the Marquis.
Anyone within these walls is his guest!
Furthermore, any guest of the Marquis is under the protection of Archduke Raondeal.
Know this!
When you strike this gate with your cudgels,
you strike the foot of His Grace's throne!
Retreat for now!
That's quite a commotion so late at night.
What's going on here?
I apologize for the disturbance.
I offer my deepest gratitude for your sanctuary.
Save your gratitude for Marquis Milone, though he's not here to hear it.
What did they want?
They're undoubtedly lackeys from Medio Trading.
That was my thought.
They caught wind of my business with you, so they were sent to prevent it from—
Prevent it?
I believe that my companion was captured.
Can you help me rescue her?
After the commotion here, I sent some of my men to follow them.
They reported seeing a young lady being taken, apparently against her will.
That must have been my companion, Holo.
She chose to act as a decoy so that I could make it here.
I see.
But why would they want to capture Miss Holo?
I already—
I expect it's because we joined with your company in trying to obstruct their plans.
Don't you think that's strange?
What's strange?!
Please calm down.
Something is very, very wrong.
What makes you think that?
Let me put it this way.
Is there anything they could prevent by taking you two hostage?
We've already started collecting Trenni silver coins.
In other words, we understand the entirety of this opportunity.
They may have had reason to hold you hostage
if you had instructed us to collect Trenni silver coins without telling us why.
However, no company would have taken action based on such a vague suggestion.
Surely you don't mean...
I do. We already have all the information we need to turn a profit.
The fate of you and your partner changes nothing.
It's a terrible turn of events, but we've already invested a substantial amount of money.
If we had to choose between a lucrative profit and bearing your grudge,
I'm sorry to say that our interests would always come first.
However...
Oh my God.
Hold on!
I can see that your partner is important to you.
Any effort to rescue her will fail
without a calm and collected mindset.
My apologies.
That's okay.
I wouldn't be able to stay calm if my wife were in a similar situation.
Like I said, it's strange.
Medio Trading would know how our company would decide, right?
Of course.
They still went after you in spite of the fact that you would have no value in potential negotiations.
Can you think of why that might be?
A reason why...
Don't tell me...
The profits before us are colossal.
We'd very much like to see this plan succeed.
But...
Don't hesitate to say what's on your mind, no matter how trivial.
Mr. Lawrence!
There is something, right?
You do know something.
Excuse me.
What is it?
We just received a letter.
I believe it concerns our current situation.
"To the wolf and the forest in which the wolf resides"?
Excuse me, but may I take a look at the letter first?
Very well.
Thank you.
"We have the wolf."
"The Church welcomes all with open arms."
"To keep the wolf away from your home,
keep the door shut and secure your family inside."
Holo, the girl I was traveling with,
is a wolf that controls harvests in human form.
You're...
Next Episode: "Wolf and a Lovers' Quarrel".